Oh, hey. Did Rishi tell you about his spear? There's like a whole story.
He sure did. Talk about a real tearjerker, am I right?
Yeah, it was sad. I really hope he's doing okay out there.
I recently began work on my superb rebranding plan.
I'll write a book about their past. I'll spread the plain truth about their curse and persecution.
But I haven't figured out how I want to present it.
A documentary approach? Diary style? I don't think I could handle a whole odyssey.
How about a simple booklet? Say, ten pages. Packaged with a figure.
So, what are you working on?
I'm trying to write a book about Rishiard's past. His heroic exploits.
Is that all you have so far?
Yeah. I'm just getting started.
Um, I want to help. If you don't think I'd get in the way.
Huh?
Rishiard told me a lot about his past while we were traveling here together.
I think I could probably write some good stories.
Yeah? I'd love that. Although, I still want your classes to come first.
Okay.
Bye.
Aisha, if there's something on your mind, you know you can tell me, right?
What does that mean? I'm fine.
Just if you think I'm spending too much time with Norn and you want to hang out more together,
or if you're feeling overwhelmed and want to break from work.
Hmm.
Well, if I may.
I would like a salary, please.
Thank you, miss.
What do you want those for?
I collected a bunch of different flower seeds on our trip up here, so now I'd like to try and grow them.
Would that be okay?
Absolutely.
Although, maybe we should pick up some potting soil, too.
The earth around here doesn't seem the most fertile.
I was actually going to ask if you would make some for me yourself with your incredible earth magic.
Would that be okay?
Absolutely.
Thanks, Rudeus.
Pretty.
Are you getting those as a present for Sylphie?
Yep.
I'm the kind of guy who wants to treat his wife right.
Sylphie's a very lucky woman to have you.
Oh, that big brother.
I do hope you'll try to spare some of that love from me every once in a while.
Absolutely not.
Not that kind of love.
Oh.
I can't give you a better deal than this.
Come on, just a little bit lower.
If it helps you to know my older brother here is Rudeus Greyrat, the university's famous mage.
Huh?
And between us.
You know Princess Ariel?
She respects my brother and they even work together.
Greyrat, you say?
And the princess would approve.
I guess I could.
All right.
You got a deal.
Yes!
You know I don't mind chipping in a little bit if you're short.
Mm-mm.
Not to worry.
I have just enough.
See?
Wow, talk about business sense.
That's kind of intimidating.
I've always wanted to own some cute decor like this.
Lilia didn't get stuff like that for you and Millis?
No, she considered it disrespectful.
She said a maid shouldn't buy furnishings to suit her own taste.
But you're okay with it?
Absolutely.
Next, we'll focus on summoning organic matter from our old world.
Organic?
Yes.
Hopefully food.
Is the step with the detailed conditions really necessary?
Yes.
I don't want to teleport myself back to a foreign country or the middle of the ocean.
Right, that makes sense.
So she'll get closer and closer to summoning something as complex as a human being,
then teleport herself back to Japan with pinpoint accuracy.
Defining the conditions can be tricky, so I'll need to visit the old man again for that.
The mysterious summoning authority you vaguely mentioned?
Yeah.
Now, not to change the subject or anything,
but here, your reward for the bottle.
What is it?
A summoning scroll for a lamplight spirit.
It will float along behind the caster, emitting a bright light.
Though, it will fade as its mana dwindles.
That's an original.
The old man designed it himself,
and not even the Mage's Guild has access to it.
What Japanese guy doesn't go nuts for limited editions?
And if our next experiment succeeds,
I'll give you something even better.
So please, I'm counting on your help.
Zanoba, meanwhile, finally finished making a figure with his own hands,
and gave it to Julie as a gift.
Thanks, Master.
You was welcome, Master.
I will cherish this forever.
You're very welcome.
Keep up the good work.
Okay.
Man.
Zanoba giving away a figure.
Isn't that nice, Julie?
You take good care of it now.
After helping Rue Jird bring my sisters here,
Ginger chose to go back to work for Zanoba.
A decision which I can't say I understand.
But she's also been teaching Julie etiquette.
She's helped her make huge strides in speaking the human tongue as well.
And she says she rented a room near the school,
which makes her sound more like a commuter wife than a knight.
What do you need?
Nothing.
I guess I was just wondering what made you pledge your fealty to Zanoba.
Because Prince Zanoba's mother asked me to.
She personally entrusted his care to me.
I devoted myself to him then and there.
I swore I would serve him until my dying breath.
Wow.
That sounds like a really moving story.
Then what?
That's all there is.
I don't have any subordinates.
Ginger was my last guard, but I traded her to Pax for the Roxy figure.
What a fantastic bargain that was.
How can she stay loyal to him after he treated her like that?
I guess families do come in all shapes and sizes.
I haven't found a full cure yet.
Only this method of suppression.
This prototype can force in external mana, counter to the flow of her internal mana.
So at the very least, it can relieve Alina Lisa's symptoms.
But there are two major problems.
That's not bad.
I guess the first problem is it's horrible.
Indeed it is.
I wouldn't wear it.
But I do believe with Zonaba and Silent's help, I can at least make it smaller.
Then what's the second problem?
Even for a prototype, it drains far too much mana.
It only lasts an hour.
Lisa can't recharge it at all without me.
And since that limits us to conducting only a few tests a day, I thought to call you.
Would you mind charging it?
Yeah, of course.
I'm always happy to help.
I appreciate that.
So Cliff is making slow but steady progress toward his goals too.
Good.
Good for him.
I'd say I've found a really nice rhythm lately.
I work out.
I eat breakfast.
I go to school, see friends, check in on how everyone's research is going.
I help Norn study.
Then go home for some family time.
Every day looks about the same, but I'm still making progress step by step.
I never managed anything like this last time.
I think this is what you call real happiness.
I need a bath.
What are you doing up?
It's still so early.
Oh gosh.
Now that it's time, I'm kind of starting to get cold feet.
You have nothing to be afraid of.
You can do it, Sophie.
Show some courage.
Rudy, you should know, I haven't had a you-know-what in two months.
And, well, I haven't been feeling so great lately, so I was starting to wonder.
Anyway, Aisha went with me to see the neighborhood doctor.
And, um, turns out that I'm probably expecting.
Is that okay?
Say something.
Is it okay if I feel?
Huh?
Oh, of course.
Go right ahead.
Brother dear, don't you have anything to say?
Your wife is waiting for you.
Thank you.
I love you.
What?
Why are you thanking me?
Sorry.
I just...
I don't know.
I can't find the words.
Rudy, you wanted kids pretty badly, didn't you?
Ahem.
Big brother.
Your wife is in a delicate condition, so for the time being...
All right.
Wow, I'm gonna be an aunt, huh?
Congratulations!
Aunt Norn, I like that.
Princess Ariel indicated that Miss Sylphia's relief from her duties for at least two years.
And while you're on family leave, great Aunt Alina Lise will assume your bodyguard duties.
You'll need the time off.
Is Grandma going to be okay with that?
She's still got her curse.
She personally assured me she could manage.
I wouldn't worry.
I informed the rest of your circle as well.
They're happy for you both.
They promised me they'd check on you.
They did?
Thank you, Aisha.
Oh, any time, brother dear.
Thanks for this meal.
I was thinking.
Dad is probably gonna be shocked when he shows up and finds out he's a grandpa.
Oh yeah, he'll be so surprised.
That's for sure.
Yeah.
Guys like him love to spoil their grandchildren.
He'll be happy.
I'll never forget how over the moon he was when you two were born.
That's our daddy.
I can't wait.
Sylphia and I got married and our whole family will be here.
The paradise I dreamed of back in Buena Village is almost a reality.
Zenith Rescue in dire state.
Send help immediately.
Hi!
Oh, great.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
The letter from Geese.
He said they're having trouble rescuing Zenith and that they need help.
You're not wrong.
Sounds like trouble indeed.
You think?
Come on!
You told me I'd regret going to Begarit.
Why did you trick me?
Trick you?
No, no, no.
If you go to Begarit, you will regret it.
That much has not changed.
Ah, okay.
I see.
That's how this plays out.
What you're trying to tell me here is...
I'm gonna regret it if I go to Begarit.
Also, I'll regret not going.
That right?
No, it's not like that.
Think about it.
Did you regret it until yesterday?
You made lots of friends.
You met all sorts of people and did a bit of growing yourself.
Your condition was cured and you made up with your sisters.
Also...
You got married and now you're a papa.
Sure, it hasn't been bad.
I'll admit it.
But still, it's wrong.
You lied.
You said I shouldn't go to Begarit.
You tricked me.
Take it easy.
There's no trick.
In fact, I'll tell you what I told you then.
Steer clear of the Begarit continent.
You'll regret going there.
Enough of this crap.
My family's in trouble.
At least tell me why I'll regret it.
My lips are sealed.
Damn it!
How could I forget that you're nothing but a giant asshole?
What a harsh thing to say.
My advice has always been rather helpful, no?
So what if it has?
That doesn't change the fact that you tricked me.
Please, just give me a hint of something I can use here.
What am I gonna regret, huh?
Tell me!
How do I make a choice like this without any info?
What does anyone do?
Most people make their decisions in the dark.
You sound so greedy.
I'm greedy, is that it?
Well, I don't want any regrets!
If you think about it, it's quite obvious.
You've spent a year and a half in Magic University.
Your sisters took approximately one year to reach you.
If you had gone to Begarit, you would have missed them.
Not true.
My sisters only came to me because Paul got my letter.
If I'd never sent it to him, they would have stayed put.
Either in Millis or that port town.
Think!
If you hadn't written your letter, Paul would have sent them to the Kingdom of Asura.
Lilia's got family there, don't you remember?
Fair point.
You're probably right about that.
It's the same now.
You have a wife.
You leave her and the child, and then?
What happens when you're traveling to Begarit?
Do you plan on leaving your family alone while you hike across the world?
I see.
I can't avoid regrets.
That's the deal.
Right.
Regret is inevitable, no matter how hard you try.
If you go to Begarit, you'll miss out on a great opportunity.
So I suggest that you stay.
Well, if you're this adamant, then sounds like there's only one choice.
Final stay.
Really?
Great!
You want some advice?
Sure.
How much worse could it get?
Rudeus, stay home until next mating season.
When it comes, Lidia and Persina will pounce at you relentlessly.
You shall choose to have relations with one of them.
And if you do this, your life will be filled with even greater happiness in the end.
Now you want me to cheat on my wife?
I've already made up my mind.
Sylvie is the only one.
And the girls and I are just friends.
It's not like that, damn it!
Rudy, are you okay?
Was it a nightmare?
I'm okay.
Lidia and Persina aside, the man-god had a point.
No matter how hard I think about a decision, I can never be certain about the outcome.
I can only be certain about one thing.
It'll take me at least a year to reach Begarit.
It's that letter.
You can't seem to get it off your mind.
Listen, Rudy.
It's not just you.
Your sisters are concerned as well.
But please don't worry about me.
I'll be fine, okay?
I'm not going.
I'll stay with you.
Send help immediately.
I wonder what went wrong.
The letter did come from Geese, not Paul.
Maybe he sent it in a moment of panic before he met up with Paul's group.
They might have rescued Zenith already.
If I go now, there's a chance I could miss them.
But what if...
Wise choice, Rudeus.
You're better off staying behind for this one.
So that's how it is.
You're going?
You sure you should?
As Sylphie's grandmother, I'd like to do something to help her family.
That's noble, but what about poor Cliff?
I'll break up with him.
What else can I do?
He'll wait for you if you explain yourself.
Yes, but that boy has the makings of a future Pope.
It would be selfish of me to hold him back.
He's better off remembering me as a youthful indiscretion.
Leaving it at that will be the best thing for his career.
Ah, yes, I see.
I'm sure you'll deal with this matter easily enough and be back before too long.
I will remain here and continue to pursue my research, but I will be praying for your speedy return.
I kind of thought you'd ask me not to go or demand to join.
Should you wish for me to accompany you, Master, I would be loathe to refuse.
But being unaccustomed to lengthy journeys, I fear I might prove to be a burden.
Besides, I could hardly imagine taking Julie on such a long trek.
Well, what about me?
You think I should go?
That's for you to decide, Master.
If I may, allow me to offer one piece of advice.
A child never stops growing, with or without their father.
If you're worried about your parents, I suggest you go.
I'll guarantee the safety of your wife and sisters in your absence.
Although, if it were up to me, of course, I'd never want to leave your side.
That means a lot.
Sylphie won't be alone.
My sisters are here with her.
She'll do just fine without me.
And yet, I still feel torn as the pillar of this family.
As a husband and a father, I have a duty to stay by their side.
They're my world now.
I can't just leave them like this.
Where are you going, Norn?
Norn!
Hey, are you okay?
I just thought, if you won't go, I guess it's up to me then.
Oh, Norn, you won't make it.
But, Rudius, please.
Mom and Ted are in trouble.
They need our help.
So why?
Tell me!
Why are you going to help them, big brother?
Just go!
You're so much stronger!
And you're fit to travel, so...
Why not?
Rudy!
She's right.
I can do it.
Unlike me, she can't go, no matter how much she wants to.
But me...
I can.
Hey, Norn.
I'll go find them.
Will you watch the house while I'm gone?
Yes.
Please don't fight with your sister.
And help out Sylphie when you can, okay?
Okay.
All right.
Good girl.
Please help them.
For me.
For us.
I'm going to save our family.